<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<!-- html-formatted errorbox messages -->
	<string name="campaign_info_errorbox_stopped">
		<![CDATA[
		<b>warning:</b> this campaign is <b>stopped</b>, meaning that you can no longer submit surveys for it.
		]]>
	</string>
	
	<string name="campaign_info_errorbox_invalid_role">
		<![CDATA[
		<b>warning:</b> you don\'t seem to have sufficient permission to access this campaign at this time.
		]]>
	</string>
	
	<!-- explanatory text sections -->
	<string name="campaign_info_privacy_details">
		<![CDATA[
		The <b>privacy</b> of the campaign determines who can view the shared data associated with the campaign.
		Remember, all data is private until you mark it shared on-line.<br /><br />

		A campaign may be in one of two privacy states:<br />
		* <b>private</b>: only you and the administrator can see your data, even if it is shared.<br />
		* <b>shared</b>: administrators, authors and analysis can see your shared data.<br />
		]]>
	</string>

	<string name="campaign_info_status_details">
		<![CDATA[
		The above displays the status of the campaign. <br /><br />

		Normally, you are either <b>participating</b> in a campaign, meaning the associated surveys are available
		for you to complete on your phone, or the campaign is <b>available for participation</b> meaning that you
		can download the campaign and its surveys to your phone. Any other status indicates that there\'s a problem with the campaign.
		]]>
	</string>
	
	<string name="survey_info_status_details">
		<![CDATA[
		The above displays the status of the campaign to which this survey belongs.<br /><br />

		Normally, this is <b>participating</b>, meaning that you can submit a survey for the campaign.
		Any other status indicates that there\'s a problem with the campaign.
		]]>
	</string>
	
	<string name="campaign_info_responses_details">
		<![CDATA[
		The above count is the number of responses you have submitted for all surveys in this campaign.
		]]>
	</string>
	
	<string name="survey_info_responses_details">
		<![CDATA[
		The above count is the number of responses you have submitted for this survey.
		]]>
	</string>
	
	<string name="campaign_info_triggers_details">
		<![CDATA[
		The above count is the number of reminders configured for this campaign.<br /><br />
		
		Tap the bell icon in the action bar to configure the reminders.
		]]>
	</string>
	
	<string name="survey_info_triggers_details">
		<![CDATA[
		The above count is the number of reminders configured for this survey.
		]]>
	</string>
</resources>
